showingtime.com 2019-10-04

# Privacy Policy | ShowingTime

This website, www.ShowingTime.com, and all software and services accessible through this website (collectively, the “ _Site_ “) is operated by ShowingTime.com or any successor in interest thereto (the “ _Company_ ,” “ _we_ ,” “ _us_ “). Your privacy is very important to us, and this Online Privacy Policy (“ _Privacy Policy_ “) is being provided as a notice to you to describe the types of information we collect about you through this Site, how we use this information, and how we protect it.

This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect at this Site only. We may update our Privacy Policy periodically, so please check back here for the latest version of our Privacy Policy.

## Online Information Collection

We do not collect any personal information at our Site, other than the information you choose to supply to us voluntarily. You expressly authorize ShowingTime to share this information with the buyer’s and seller’s agents and brokers and personnel from each of their companies, as necessary to perform the services of our products. We do not collect any sensitive information at our Site, and request that you do not submit any such information to us through the Site. We define “ _personal information_ ” as information that is unique to you or any other person, and might include a name, address, phone number, and email address. We define “ _sensitive information_ ” as information that might include a Social Security number, account numbers, or medical information about you or any other person. If you encounter a screen or page that requests information you do not want to share with us, do not enter the information and do not proceed with that screen or page. However, if you choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with the services dependent upon the collection of this information, such as setting up an appointment time and providing your personal information and appointment with another agent or brokerage company in connection with the property you are inquiring about. You represent that you have all necessary permissions to submit all information which you submit to us, including any information you submit about a third party.

You may be registered or unregistered when you use our Site. As a registered user, we require, at a minimum, your name, address, and e-mail address. We may contact you when necessary, to follow up on the status of your registration, your opinion of certain aspects of our Site, or to provide you with additional information you may need about our products and services.

If you do provide us with personal information on this Site, we will only use it for the purposes described where it is collected, and in this Privacy Policy. We will use your personal information to tailor our content, forward information to you or about you to others regarding appointment times, locations of real property and related appointment information. Your personal information is necessary to provide the full functionality of the ShowingTime For The MLS and/or ShowingTime Lead Alert services. We will not sell or rent your personal information for marketing purposes to a third party without your express consent, or as provided below. We will use de-identified information and personal information for our internal analysis of the Site, and as further described below.

We will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of the Company unless (1) you expressly authorize us to do so, (2) it is necessary to allow our contractors or agents to provide services for us, (3) it is necessary in order to provide our products or services to you, (4) it is necessary in connection with a proposed sale of some or all assets or equity of the Company, and such disclosure is made subject to a confidentiality agreement regarding personal information containing requirements not less stringent than those of this Privacy Policy; or (5) we are required or permitted by law. If you engage in activities such as spoofing, spamming, the posting of libelous, slanderous, defamatory, or infringing materials, or other unlawful acts, we may be required to disclose your personal information and other identifying information to our web hosting provider, third parties or to government authorities. We may also use the personal information you choose to provide to us to improve the content of our Site.

We may aggregate statistics that we gather about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and services, including, for example, the number of appointments made in a geographic area, the number of agents from each company that used the Site, the number of cancellations, the relative ranking and use of the Site by different companies and/or their agents. We may provide this information to third parties on a de-identified basis. We may select outside companies to provide services on our behalf and use de-identified information in the course of measuring the number of visits, average time spent, page views, and other statistics about visitors to our Site, in general. We may also use this data to monitor Site performance and to make the Site easier and more convenient to use.

This Site does not engage in the collection of personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services. We have not authorized any third party to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you visit this Site. Thus, this Site does not respond to web browser “do not track” track signals or other similar mechanisms.

## We Use Your IP Address and Web Browser

We use your IP address as well as the URL of the web page you were just on (known as the “Refer”) to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Site, and to communicate with you after you have sent us e-mails. We also collect and use the browser version you are using to access our Site.

## Confidentiality and Security: Personal Information

If you choose to provide personal information to us voluntarily via this Site, we restrict access to such personal information to our employees or others who need to know that information to provide services to you or in the course of conducting our normal business operations. We maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect such personal information.

## Confidentiality and Security: Sensitive Information

Please do not submit any sensitive information about yourself or others through the Site. The Site is not intended to collect sensitive information and therefore we cannot be responsible for the protection of any sensitive information that you may submit to us via the Site.

## Right to Verify the Accuracy of Information We Collect

Keeping information accurate and up to date is important to us. An individual may see and correct their personal information that they provided to us, subject to certain legal or contractual limitations. Contact us at the address provided below if you wish to verify your personal information.

## Information Collected from Children

We are strongly committed to preserving online privacy for all of our website visitors, including children. The Site is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children or sell products to children. Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you are not permitted to submit information to the Site.

## Email

We appreciate your questions and comments about our Site, products and services and welcome your email messages to mailboxes listed on our Sites. We will share your messages with those within our organization that are most capable of addressing the issues contained in your message. We will keep a copy of your message until we have had an opportunity to address your concerns. We may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it, but your email address will not be used for any other purpose. If you provide e-mail feedback about the site or our services we may publish that feedback on our site using your name. If you send us e-mails, from time to time we may send updates to you about services which may be of interest to you.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of information that a web server may place on your computer when you visit a site. Cookies are commonly used by sites to improve the user experience. Many cookies last only through a single site session or visit. Others may have an expiration date, or may remain on your computer until you delete them.

We may use cookies for a number of purposes – for example, to maintain continuity during a user session, to gather data about the usage of our Site for research and other purposes, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information, or to store a user name or identification number so that you do not have to provide this information every time you return to our Site.

Our cookies will track only your activity relating to your online activity on this Site, and will not track your other Internet activity. Our cookies do not gather personal information other than such information that you supply.

You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. However, if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to use certain of our Site features.

We may occasionally use other companies to set cookies on our Site and gather cookie information for us. In some cases, we may also use another company to operate web servers for our Site. We use the cookie information gathered by these companies in the same manner as stated above.

In addition to the information we collect from cookies, we also obtain information which you provide to us online. In some cases, we retain both the cookie information and/or the information you provide to us online – for example, to complete a transaction you requested or to keep historical records of your past transactions. In other cases we only retain the cookie and/or online information you give us if you request us to do so for your use in subsequent sessions.

## Links to Other Sites

For your convenience, we may provide links to other sites that we do not control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any sites not under our control and we do not endorse any of these sites, the services or products described or offered on such sites, or any of the content contained on those sites.

## Change in Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy is reflected by the version date located at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.

Contacting us – If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please write to us at [webmaster@ShowingTime.com](mailto:webmaster@ShowingTime.com).

 _Last Updated: September 25, 2017_
